<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2023 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     https://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Affirmations</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">I am strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">I believe in myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Each day is a new opportunity to grow and be a better version of myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Every challenge in my life is an opportunity to learn from.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">I have so much to be grateful for.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Good things are always coming into my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">New opportunities await me at every turn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">I have the courage to follow my heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things will unfold at precisely the right time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">I will be present in all the moments that this day brings.</string>
    <string name="affirmation11">I am having a positive and inspiring impact on the people I come into contact with.</string>
    <string name="affirmation12">I am inspiring people through my work.</string>
    <string name="affirmation13">I’m rising above the thoughts that are trying to make me angry or afraid.</string>
    <string name="affirmation14">Today is a phenomenal day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation15">I am turning DOWN the volume of negativity in my life, while simultaneously turning UP the volume of positivity.</string>
    <string name="affirmation16">I am filled with focus.</string>
    <string name="affirmation17">I am not pushed by my problems; I am led by my dreams.</string>
    <string name="affirmation18">I am grateful for everything I have in my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation19">I am independent and self-sufficient.</string>
    <string name="affirmation20">I can be whatever I want to be.</string>
    <string name="affirmation21">I am not defined by my past; I am driven by my future.</string>
    <string name="affirmation22">I use obstacles to motivate me to learn and grow.</string>
    <string name="affirmation23">Today will be a productive day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation24">I am intelligent and focused.</string>
    <string name="affirmation25">I feel more grateful each day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation26">I am getting healthier every day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation27">Each and every day, I am getting closer to achieving my goals.</string>
    <string name="affirmation28">Through the power of my thoughts and words, incredible transformations are happening in me and within my life right now.</string>
    <string name="affirmation29">I am constantly growing and evolving into a better person.</string>
    <string name="affirmation30">I’m freeing myself from all destructive doubt and fear.</string>
    <string name="affirmation31">I accept myself for who I am and create peace, power and confidence of mind and of heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation32">I am going to forgive myself and free myself. I deserve to forgive and be forgiven.</string>
    <string name="affirmation33">I am healing and strengthening every day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation34">I’ve made it through hard times before, and I’ve come out stronger and better because of them. I’m going to make it through this.</string>
    <string name="affirmation35">I do not waste away a single day of my life. I squeeze every ounce of value out of each of my days on this planet—today, tomorrow, and everyday.</string>
    <string name="affirmation36">I must remember the incredible power I possess within me to achieve anything I desire.</string>
    <string name="affirmation37">I do not engage with people who try to penetrate my mind with unhelpful thoughts and ideas—I walk away when a person or a situation isn’t healthy for me.</string>
    <string name="affirmation38">I belong in this world; there are people that care about me and my worth.</string>
    <string name="affirmation39">My past might be ugly, but I am still beautiful.</string>
    <string name="affirmation40">I have made mistakes, but I will not let them define me.</string>
    <string name="affirmation41">My soul radiates from the inside and warms the souls of others.</string>
    <string name="affirmation42">I don’t compare myself to others. The only person I compare myself to is the person I was yesterday. And as long as the person I am today is even the tiniest bit better than the person I was yesterday—I’m meeting my own definition of success.</string>
    <string name="affirmation43">Note to self: I am going to make you so proud.</string>
    <string name="affirmation44">I finish what matters and let go of what does not.</string>
    <string name="affirmation45">I feed my spirit. I train my body. I focus my mind. This is my time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation46">My life has meaning. What I do has meaning. My actions are meaningful and inspiring.</string>
    <string name="affirmation47">What I have done today was the best I was able to do today. And for that, I am thankful.</string>
    <string name="affirmation48">One small positive thought in the morning can change my whole day. So, today I rise with a powerful thought to set the tone and allow success to reverberate through every moment of my day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation49">I set goals and go after them with all the determination I can muster. When I do this, my own skills and talents will take me to places that amaze me.</string>
    <string name="affirmation50">Happiness is a choice, and today I choose to be happy.</string>
    <string name="affirmation51">I am successful.</string>
    <string name="affirmation52">I am confident.</string>
    <string name="affirmation53">I am powerful.</string>
    <string name="affirmation54">I am strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation55">I am getting better and better every day.</string>
    <string name="affirmation56">All I need is within me right now.</string>
    <string name="affirmation57">I wake up motivated.</string>
    <string name="affirmation58">I am an unstoppable force of nature.</string>
    <string name="affirmation59">I am a living, breathing example of motivation.</string>
    <string name="affirmation60">I am living with abundance.</string>
</resources>
